A Finding Aid to the Ruth Bowman Papers, 1936-2006, bulk 1963-1999, in the Archives of American Art AAA.bowmruth2
Archives of American Art
- Subject Files, 1936-2006; Series 4; 9.6 Linear feet Boxes 3-13, 26
  - General Subjects, circa 1950s-1997 (Box 3)
    - KUSC "Sounds of Seeing" (Box 5)
      - Scripts, 1979-1985 (Box 5, Folder 29-30)
      - Working Files, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Lectures, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Long Beach Museum of Art, 1971-1972; includes 1 videocassette: VHS (Box 5, Folder 33-34)
    - Los Angeles City Interview Board, 1969-1975 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Los Angeles City Junior Arts Center, 1974; 1985 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Los Angeles City Municipal Art Gallery, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Los Angeles County Museum of Art (Box 5)
      - Docent Handbook, 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Education Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Education Department, 1975-1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Film, 1974-1975; includes 1 sound cassette (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Focus Program, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Joint Education Project, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Minutes and Memos, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Museum Education Program Study by Dr. Eva Schindler-Rainman, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Museum Services Council Questionnaire on American Narrative Painting, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Personnel, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Registrar, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Judah L. Magnes Memorial Museum, 1977-1982 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Maryland Center for Public Broadcasting, 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Council for the Arts at M.I.T., 1972-1987 (Box 6, Folder 12-18)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Sky Art Conference, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1970s-1980s (Box 6, Folder 20-21)
    - The Metropolitan Museum of Art and Television, 1952-1976 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Mid-Atlantic Association of Museums, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - The Missosuri State Council on the Arts, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - "Museum and Other Art Careers," New School for Social Research and Bryn Mawr College, 1973-1984; includes 1 U-Matic videocassette and 1 sound cassette (Box 6, Folder 25-26)
    - Museum Computer Conference, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - "Museum Directors' Forum" (Box 7)
      - General Information, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Eliot James - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1968 October 23; 1 sound tape reels (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Thomas Hoving - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1968 November 13; 1 sound tape reels (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Lowry, Bates - The Museum of Modern Art, 1968 October 30; 1 sound tape reels (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Messer, Thomas - Guggenheim Museum, 1968 October 16; 1 sound tape reels (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Rathbone, Perry T. - Museum of Fine Arts Boston, 1968 November 6; 1 sound tape reels (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - The Museum of Contemporary Art Los Angeles, 1980-1987 (Box 7, Folder 7-10)
    - The Museum of Contemporary Art Los Angeles, Architecture and Design Support Committee, 1982-1986 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - The Museum of Contemporary Art Los Angeles,"The Territory of Art" Radio Series, 1983-1984; includes 8 sound cassettes (Box 7, Folder 12-14)
    - The Museum of Modern Art, 1968-1986 (Box 7, Folder 15-16)
    - The Museum of Primitive Art, 1969-1970s (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Museum Services Bill Congressional Testimony, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Museum Studies Programs and Courses, 1965-1985 (Box 7, Folder 19-20)
    - Museum Training, circa 1967-1975 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - The Museum Trustee Committee for Research and Development, Inc., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Museums and Television, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - National Association of Educational Broadcasters 52nd Annual Convention, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities Grant Review Panel, 1979-1983 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - National Museum of Women in the Arts, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - National Science Foundation Grant Reviews, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Nativity in Art, circa 1942-circa 1950s (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - "New Directions for the Teaching of Art History," New York State Council on the Arts Conference, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - "New Museums/New Audiences", 1985 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - New School for Social Research Conference, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - New York City Cultural Council, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - New York City Parks, Recreation and Cultural Affairs Adminstration, 1968-1972 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - New York University, 1972-1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - New York University Art Collection (Box 8)
      - Acquisitions (1955-1966), circa 1963-1966 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Annual Reports, 1966-1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1963-1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Floor Plans, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Printed Material, circa 1960-1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - New York University Division of Continuing Education, 1965-1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - The Newark Museum, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - The Newark Museum, "Murals Without Walls: Arshile Gorky's Aviation Murals", 1978; 1 sound cassette and 3 U-Matic videocassettes (Box 8, Folder 12-15)
    - Newport Harbor Art Museum, 1975-1988 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Newsletters, Miscellaneous, 1980-1987 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Northeast Museums Conference, 1973-1977 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Nova Scotia Workshop, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - "One to One," WNYC-TV, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Palm Springs Desert Museum, Inc., 1973-1980 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Papermaking, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Photography Exhibits, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - "Privacy and Democracy in 1984: A Humanistic View of the New Communciations Technology", 1981 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Program for Art on Film, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Radio, 1971-1979 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Registrars' Report, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Robert Gore Rifkin Collection, 1974; 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Rockefeller Foundation Fellowship in Museum Education, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Rodia, Simon - Towers in Watts, 1978-1985 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Romantic Rebellion, Rogers and Cowan Film, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Ruder and Finn Fine Arts, American Express Arts Funding Project, 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - Santa Barbara Museum of Art, Preston Morton Collection, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Seattle Art Museum, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Southern California Committee for Contemporary Art Documentation, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Southern California Designer Crafts, Inc., 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Southwest Educators Symposium, Museum of Northern Arizona, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Southwest Regional Laboratory, Educational Research and Development, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Stein, Gertrude, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - "Support Systems for Arts in the 1980s", circa 1975-circa 1985; 1 sound tape reels (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Television, 1969-1983 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - "Understanding Modern Art", 1969-1973 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - University of California, Irvine, 1991-1994 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, "Art as Opera", 1983; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, Extension Department, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - University of California, Santa Barbara, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - University of Mid-America, 1976-1981 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Videos, 1975-1981 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Visual Communications Congress, "Audiovisualizing the Video Arts", 1980; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Western Association of Art Museums, 1975-1981; includes 1 sound cassette (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Western Museums Conference Annual Meeting, 1986; 6 Sound cassettes (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1979-1985 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - WNYC "Views on Art" Radio Program, circa 1973 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Women - Art, 1972-1999 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Women's City Club of New York, 1968-1977; Includes 1 sound cassette (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - WPA Art, 1996-1997; 1972 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - The Yankee Doodle Society, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - YWCA International Training Institute, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Oversized Subject File Material regarding Gorky Murals at Newark Airport from Box 5, Folder 1, 1978-1979 (Box 26)
    - Oversize Subject File Material relating to "Great Art Collections" from Box 5, Folder 2, 1969-1971 (Box 26)
  - Artists' Files, 1936-2006 (Box 9)
    - A, Miscellaneous, 1974-2001 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Andrews, Benny, circa 1975 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - B, Miscellaneous, 1959-1985 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Browne, Byron, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - C, Miscellaneous, 1967-1984 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - D, Miscellaneous, circa 1972-1983 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Eames, Charles and Ray, 1973-circa 1979 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - F-G, Miscellaneous, 1966-1984 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - H, Miscellaneous, 1963-1984 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - I-J, Miscellaneous, 1936-1983 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - K, Miscellaneous, 1968-1983 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - L, Miscellaneous, 1964-1983 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Lampert, Ellen, 1981-1984 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Levine, Les, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - M, Miscellaneous, 1979-1984 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Marshall, Vicky, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Matisse, Henri, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Monet, Claude, 1970s (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Moore, Henry, circa 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Motherwell, Robert, 1973-1984 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - N, Miscellaneous, 1963-1993 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - O-P, Miscellaneous, 1963-1984 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - R, Miscellaneous, 1963-1984 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - S, Miscellaneous, 1974-1985 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Smith, David, 1966-2006 (Box 10, Folder 18-19)
    - T-V, Miscellaneous, 1962-1984 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - W, Miscellaneous, 1972-1987 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Wilfred, Thomas, 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1946-circa 1960 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Y-Z, Miscellaneous, 1968-1985 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Ruth Bowman Activities, 1962-1988 (Box 10)
    - Activities, 1962-1965 (Box 10, Folder 25-39)
    - Activities, 1975-1988 (Box 11, Folder 1-6)
  - "Sunrise Semester", 1971-1973 (Box 11)
    - Bibliography, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Course Description, Syllabus, Final Examination, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Publicity, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Scripts 1-45, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 10-14)
    - Study Guide, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Viewers' Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 16-19)
    - Classes 1-16, 1972 September 25 - 1972 October 30; 16 sound tape reels (Box 11, Folder 20-27)
    - Classes 17-46, 1972 November 11 - 1973 January 12; 30 sound tape reels (Box 12, Folder 1-15)
- Interviews, 1963-1989; Series 5; 9.2 Linear feet Boxes 12-25
  With two exceptions, the interviews were conducted by Ruth Bowman. She is the subject of two interviews, and one KUSC "Live from Trump's" radio program was hosted by Myra Livingston.
  In 1976, while attending an arts administration program offered by the British Arts Council, Bowman inteviewed museum administrators and educators in England (6 sounds cassettes).
  Serving as an advisor to Metroplitan Museum of Art Director Thomas Hoving, Bowman interviewed more than a dozen people in 1976 concerning the benefits, drawbacks, and ramifications of the Annenberg Fine Arts Center proposed for The Metropolitan Museum of Art (12 sound cassettes). The controversial plan aroused much concern and Annenberg eventually withdrew his offer.
  Among the interviews with miscellaneous individuals (4 sound reels, 6 sound cassettes, and 2 transcripts), of particular interest is an interview with Noguchi concerning a possible commission for a sculpture at Bryn Mawr College, his mother's alma mater. A 1974 interview with Bowman concerns her work at the Los Angeles County Museum of Art.
  Bowman was the host of "Sounds of Seeing," a radio show produced by KUSC radio in Los Angeles, 1979-1983. With funding from the National Endowment for the Arts, "Sounds of Seeing" aired Bowman's interviews with artists, art historians, museum curators and directors, conservators, local politicians, and others on a wide range of art related topics (7 sound reels and 69 sound cassettes). On "Live from Trump's," a KUSC radio program broadcast from Trump's Restaurant, Bowman conversed with guests about local exhibitions and other arts events.
  Interviews with 12 American abstract artists were conducted by Ruth Bowman (Ruth Gurin at the time) as background research for her intended thesis on the subject. Plans changed, and the thesis she eventually wrote was "Thomas Pollock Anshutz, 1851-1912" (M.A., Institute of Fine Arts, New York University, 1971).
  "Views on Art," her weekly radio show on WNYC, 1967-1973, featured interviews with artists, museum directors and curators, gallery owners and others who discussed their work and current exhibitions. Other topics covered include: art forgeries, underground movie making, museum management, art publishing, business and the arts, art and public relations, computers and the humanities, new art technologies, and trends in art education. (72 sound reels, 3 sound cassettes, and 1 transcript; digitized on 58 CDs).
  Interviews concerning the Annenberg Fine Arts Center, interviews of miscellaneous individuals, and WNYC "Views on Art" radio programs are alphabetized by interviewee. Those with museum administrators and educators are arraned chronologically, as are the interviews for KUSC radio shows "Sounds of Seeing" and "Live From Trump's." "Sounds of Seeing" interviews are housed in 1 folder and 4 smaller boxes within Box 14. Additional interviews recorded for other purposes are scattered among the subject files (series 4).
  - Museum Administrators and Educators, 1976 (Box 12)
    Interviews are arranged chronologically.
    - Mrs. A. Cox, National Portrait Gallery, London; Justin Morris, British Museum, 1976 August 5; 1976 August 2; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Francis Warp, Victoria and Albert Museum; Madeline Mainstone, 1976 August 6; 1976 August 5; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Brenda Capstick; A. Moore, 1976 August 6; 1976 August 9; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Annenberg Fine Arts Center, The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1976 (Box 13)
    Recordings are arranged alphabetically by name of interviewee. Some related records are found with the subject files (series 4).
    - Ackerman, J., 1964 April 14; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Alexander, Grace George, 1976 September 10; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Ambrosio, 1976 April 13; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Conner, Russell and Dale R., 1976 June 8; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Crowdis, Don, 1976; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Hoving, Thomas, 1976; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Islin, 1976 June 17; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Meyer, Karl, 1976; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Moore, A. and Nancy Thomas, 1976 August 13; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Sandlin, Daniel J., 1976 May 19; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Seardinger, Gene, 1976 September 9; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Wilson, Rodney, 1976 August 2; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Individuals, 1964-1976 (Box 13)
    Arranged alphabetically by name of interviewee.
    - Albers, Josef, interviewed by Ruth Gurin [Bowman], 1964 October 29; 1 sound tape reels (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - [Bowman], Ruth Gurin, interviewed by Duncan MacDonald, WQXR radio, 1964 February 23; 1 sound tape reels (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Bowman, Ruth with unidentified interviewer, 1974 November 13; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Burkhardt, Hans, interviewed by Ruth Bowman, 1976 November; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Burns, Edward, friend of Alice B.Toklas, interviewed by Ruth Bowman (transcript), undated; circa 1970 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Holty, Carl, interviewed by Ruth Bowman, 1967; 2 sound tape reels (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Ianco-Starrels, Josine, interviewed by Ruth Bowman (transcript), 1989 June 15 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Noguchi, Isamu, interviewed by Ruth Bowman, undated; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Shefrin, "The World of Franklin and Jefferson", circa 1977; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Sloan, Helen Farr (Mrs. John Sloan), interviewed by Ruth Bowman (transcript), 1976 November 8; Includes 2 sound cassettes (Box 13, Folder 22-23)
  - KUSC "Sounds of Seeing", 1979-1983 (Box 14)
    Sound cassettes are housed in 4 smaller boxes (A-D) within Box 14.
    - H. W. Janson; "Benjamin Franklin's Armonica", circa 1980; 1 sound tape reels (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Michael Quick on Santa Claus, 1979 December 12; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Ann S. Harris, 1979 December 13; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Kevin Donahue on "The Golden Age of Venetian Painting", 1979 December 20; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Robert Pincus; Nancy Blomberg and Brian Drake on Maori Exhibition at Museum of Natural History, Los Angeles; Gwynn Murill; Sue Ann Robinson, circa 1980-circa 1983; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Cynthia Rush on "William Rush", 1980 January 3; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Dick Weiss on "Four Leaders in Glass" at Craft and Folk Art Museum, 1980 January 25; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Athena Tacha, 1980 January 10; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Thomas Hoving on Hayam, 1980 March 2; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Constance Glenn, Elizabeth Shaw; Jack Baur on American Impressionism, 1980 March 28-1980 March 29; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Donald Firth on "Drawing, Abstract of Intent", 1980 April 1; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Sidney Janis Collection, 1980-04-09; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Lee Kimche; Stephen Weil, Hirshhorn Musuem, 1980 April 16; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Lawrence Reger, American Association of Museums, Executive Director; Gail Becker, Institute of Conemporary Art, 1981 February 18; 1980 April 17; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Shirley Sun, Deputy Director for Public Programs, National Endowment for the Humanities, 1980 April 18; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Monroe Price, 1980 May 8; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Jake Zeitlin, 1980 June 18; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Stephanie Baron, Los Angeles County Museum of Art and Gail Harrison Roman, Columbia; Frank Gehry, Paul Lubowicki and Paul Zygas, 1980 June 18; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Patterson Simms, Whitney Musuem of American Art, 1980 June 30; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Patrick Ela and Edith Wylie on Collection Policy for the Craft and Folk Art Museum, 1980 July 1; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Kathryn Smith, Schindler House, 1980 July 21; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Karen Copeland and Marcel Page, Craft and Folk Art Museum, 1980 July 22; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Local Government and the Arts; Rug dealers Al Taylor and Valerie Justin; Schindler House, Kathryn Smith; Santa Ana's Bowers Museum Albert Boime, 1980 July 31-1980 September 4; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Councilman Joel Wachs, 1980 August 19; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Eli Broad, Chairman, Board of Trustees, Musuem of Contemporary Art Los Angeles, 1980 August 22; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Otto Nazler, "Opening the Kiln", 1980 August 25; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Hon. William Norris, Museum of Contemporary Art Los Angeles, 1980 September 1; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Martin Weill, Los Angeles Conservancy; Joseph Giobanni and Barbara Goldstein on "Illusive Muse"; Ron Rakow on Edward Curtis; John Pastier on Bunker Hill, 1980 September 11-1980 October 2; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - June Wayne, Craft and Folk Art Museum; Joel Wachs and Rod Punt on Cultural Affairs Dept.; Rose Slivka; George Rodart; Charles Penny, 1980 October 9-1980 November 2; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Pontius Hulten, 1980 November 5; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Pontius Hulten; Ruth Weissman on A. Quincy Jones; Sandy Fox; Claire Isaacs, 1980 November 27-1980 December 12; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Max Palevsky, Museum of Contemporary Art Los Angeles, 1980 December 3; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - John Walsh, Los Angeles County Museum of Art, on "Thyssen", 1980 December 8; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - John Walsh; Kathy Huffman on Video Art; Max Palevsky; Judith Wechler, 1981 January 1-1981 January 15; 1981 January 1-1981 January 5; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Luxor, Egypt, Oriental Institute; Lanny Bell, Director of Chicago House, 1981 January 5; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Hal Glickman, Skirball Museum; Basil Jenkins; Egypt Today, 1981 January 20-1981 February 19; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Nancy Blomberg on Hawaii Exhibit, 1981 March 3; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Hawaii Exhibit, 1981 March 3; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Hawaii Exhibit; Bernard Kester; Edward Maeder; Judith Hoffberg, 1981 March 5-1981 March 26; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Edward Maeder, 1981 March 18; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Fred Croten; Fundraiser; Betty Klausner; Josine Ianco-Starrels; Frank Ramirez, 1981 April 2-1981 June 4; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Tony Duquette and Bill McCann; Cathy La Scolo, Getty; Lois Boardman, California Design, 1981 June 2-1981 June 18; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Jacobina Caro, 1981 summer; 1981 July; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Jacobina Caro; Helen Lundeberg, July 1981; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Maurice Tuchman, Los Angeles County Musuem of Art, 1981 July 15; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Julian and Joanne Ganz; Sid Felson; George Ellis, 1981July 21-1981 September 22; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Robert Fitzpartick, President, California Institute of the Arts and Vice President for Cultural Affairs, Los Angeles Olympic Committee, 1981 August; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Jacobina Caro, 1981 August; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Suzanne Muchnic; Leonard Fleischer, 1981 September 1; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Leonard Fleischer; Robert H. Gray, UCLA, 1981 September; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Edward Carter, 1981 September 29; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Ekpo Ayo; Margaret Welch; Thomas Hoving, 1981 October; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Bill Lillys, Los Angeles County Museum of Art; William Leischer, 1981 October 14-1981 November 10; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Gail Levin; Will Barnet, 1981 December 23-1982 January 22; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Bob Peck; John David Mooney, 1982 January 30; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - James Turrell; Wally Dawes, 1982 May 5-1982 September 1; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Ruth Weisberg; Betty Kausner; H. Shore; Sheila Tepper, 1982 May 18-1982 June 9; 1982 May 9-1982 summer; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Jacobina Caro, 1982 June 28; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 14, Folder 5)